Guide to the Yale Club of New York City Photograph Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Club of New York City photograph collection
1873-1964
RU 777
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.5
(2 boxes)
The collection contains photographs and pictures collected by the Yale Club of New York City, including some original artwork.
Yale Club of New York City
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 48-A (YRG 48-A), Yale pictorial records and collections.
Arrangement
Arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains photographs and pictures collected by the Yale Club of New York City, including some original artwork.
Photographs; Yale Club of New York City; Yale University -- Pictorial works
- Photographs, Series I
  - Henry Howland, Yale 1854 [damaged], undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Harkness Tower sketch by J. Diedricksen [damaged], undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dinner given to Liang Tun Yen by his classmates of Yale '82 [damaged], 1910 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Kick-off" for Yale-Princeton championship game [damaged], 1904 November (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Osborn Hall [damaged], undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Old Campus [damaged], undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Jess Willard standing over Jack Johnson while the referee in counting [photo made at Havana] [damaged], undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Connecticut Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Old Campus, New Haven Green, Old State House, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Farnam Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Benjamin Silliman statue outside Farnam Hall, undated
  - North Sheffield Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sterling Memorial Library, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sterling-Sheffield-Strathcona Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gateway, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified sports team, 1885 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Interior of Mory's - The Green Cup on table, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Harvard crew, 1847 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1884S (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1890 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Old Chapel interiors, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dwight Chapel interior, 1946 August 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Treasury, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Classbook committee '17S, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Intercollegiate champions golf team, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sketch by James S. King, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Archway, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Morse and Stiles courtyard, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Graduation procession outside Commons, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified banquet [sports?], undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Harkness Tower, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sterling Memorial Library, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - John Hart 1703 B.A. Diploma [copy] (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1872 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Old college pump, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Men on Old Campus fence, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Chapel Street north toward Durfee, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dwight Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dwight Hall, Alumni Hall, Durfee Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Chittenden Hall - Recitation Building, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - New Haven Green, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Elihu Yale, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Luther Tucker, George Stewart, Bill Phelps, James Angell, unidentified men [in academic robes], undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Nathaniel Shipman, Yale 1848, U.S. Circuit Court judge, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Elihu B. Frost, Howard H. Knapp, Franklin E. Worcester, Louis K. Hull, Henry T. Folsom, circa 1882 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Graduating class of 1872 in Old Chapel, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Room interiors, circa 1898, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sketch of Harkness Tower by Loring Gary Calkins, '06S, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Jay Coe, class of 1898, in room, circa 1898 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Room of Samuel B. Hawley and Albert Lucas, class of 1884S, circa 1884 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Lighthouse Point, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - East Rock, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Unidentified individuals and small groups [19thcentury], undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Unidentified small groups [20thcentury], undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Unidentified indiviuals [20thcentury], undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Athletics
    - Gerald Chittenden '01, circa 1901 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - "Tom" Johnson [Medical School], undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Phil Kanzig, Captain [Law School], undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Paul Lincoln Mitchell '01 [crew], circa 1901 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Cam Waterman '01, circa 1901 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Coach John Kennedy, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Fred Allen, Captain 1899 and 1900, circa 1900 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Football teams, 1881, 1891, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Baseball teams [including 1881 Freshman], 1881, 1882, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Track teams, 1887, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Kent Hall and Sloane Physics Laboratory, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Battell Chapel, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Connecticut Hall, 1934 March (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Peabody Museum, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Welch Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)